## Lawrence Hebia

## Front End Web Developer

🛮 lhebia@gmail.com 🕏 lawrencehebia.com in lhebia 📢 lhebia 📞 4169034532 😲 Toronto, ON

A passionate, collaborative and creative Front End Web Developer continuing to expand his skillset. Highly skilled in JavaScript, React, SASS, API consumption with excellent customer relations experience, strong communication & interpersonal skills and a strong understanding of web design principles.

	Skills	
• React	• Git	• Gatsby
• CSS3	<ul> <li>Accessibility</li> </ul>	• REST API
• Sass	• Redux	<ul> <li>TypeScript</li> </ul>
	• CSS3	<ul><li>React</li><li>Git</li><li>CSS3</li><li>Accessibility</li></ul>

## Projects

**Devcompile,** Technologies: React, REST API, Firebase ☑

A social feed based off of the Dev.to articles API that gives the user the ability to browse articles, filter through articles, and save article details for later consumption.

Noah's Ark, Technologies: JQuery, Sass 🛮

Developed an interactive and fully accessible memory matching game using unicode emoji's, JQuery and Sass.

Password Generator, Technologies: TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3 ☑

I often generated complex passwords in one of my roles and I built this tool to help me make that easier and provide that functionality to others.

Professional Experience		
04/2019 - 09/2020	MaRS Discovery District, Business Application Specialist ☑ Performed technical business analysis, created user-facing documentation & designed and developed Cybersecurity and internal tools training programs.	
06/2017 - 04/2019	MaRS Discovery District, IT Service Lead ☑ Worked to ensure optimal service desk operations through documentation, reporting and providing support and feedback to service desk technicians.	
05/2014 - 05/2017	Apple Inc., Technical Specialist ☑ Provide insightful advice and friendly, hands-on technical support to help customers fall back in love with their products.	
Education		
05/2020 - 07/2020	Juno College of Technology, Web Development Bootcamp Certificate   Completed part-time JavaScript Enrolled in part-time Full Stack Development	
11/2018 - 12/2018	General Assembly, Part-Time Web Development Bootcamp	
09/2011 - 05/2015	Ryerson University, Bachelor of Commerce Major in Information Technology Management Minor in Law	